tweetmixx.com 2011-04-01

# Privacy Policy - Mixx

The short version is that we will never, ever sell or share your information. But our lawyers would only let us write the "nice" version if we made it long enough to look official, so to spare you their not-so-sprightly legalese, we must comply.

### Privacy Policy Updates

Because things change so quickly these days, we may have to update our privacy policy from time to time. We'll post these updates to Mixx and email updates to registered users.

### How and Why We Collect and Use Information

You don' have to give us any of your personal information use Mixx. But we might ask you to provide feedback, participate in contests, discussions, message boards, or when you register as a member of the Mixx community ("Mixxer"). So we may collect this information. Also, remember: any information you add to the public portion of your Mixx profile will be available to us as well as to other member of the Mixx community.

And yes, we may occasionally send you a targeted ad; we have to eat too, you know!

### Children's Privacy

Kids are adorable. So are puppies. We don't think Mixx is appropriate for either. We do not knowingly collect or save any information from children under the age of 13.

### Cookies

We may use cookies to improve your Mixx experience. These cookies do not generally allow us to personally identify a specific user.

### Disclosure

We may need to share your information with any of the companies that help provide the Mixx service; we'll make them to sign a confidentiality agreement, too. If, of course, we're required by law or government regulation, or of the company changes hands, we'll have to fork it over. But basically, as we said before: We're not going to sell or share your personal information.

### Links to Third Party Sites

If you follow any of the links you find on Mixx, our privacy policy stops at the door. Whenever you go to another site, you have to abide by their terms of use and are subject to their privacy policies.

### Security

To help protect your personal information we may use a few security measures, including encryption and password protection.

### Correction and Updating Your Info

If you need to, you can review, correct and delete any part of your Mixx profile, but information you post in other areas of Mixx can't be deleted. We can, however, remove the references to your icon and/or Mixx ID from your postings. Just send a request to us at the contact email below or access your account online.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, send us via email at [info@mixx.com](mailto:info@mixx.com).

The full-on legalese version of this privacy policy can be found [over here](http://www.mixx.com/privacy_legalese).
